The art of persuasion means convincing others to agree with your point of view or to follow your course of action.
说服的艺术，就是劝服他人认同你的观点，或者遵循你的行动方案。
For some of us, persuasion is an instinctive quality and the power of influencing comes naturally.
对我们当中的一些人来说，说服力是一种出于本能的特质，影响他人的能力也是与生俱来的。
For the rest of us, persuasion skills can be learned and developed over time.
而对我们当中其余的人来说，说服技能可以随着时间的推移习得和培养。
Employers place a great value on employees with persuasion skills because they can impact several aspects of job performance.
雇主非常看重具备说服技能的员工，因为这些技能能够影响工作表现的多个方面。
Besides, teamwork and leadership rely heavily on the power of persuasion to get things done.
此外，团队合作和领导力在很大程度上依靠说服力来把事情办成。
Without persuasion skills, employees may not be as committed to or convinced of the importance of an organization’s vision and long-term mission.
如果缺乏说服技能，员工可能就不会那么坚定地拥护组织的愿景和长期使命，也不会那么确信其重要性。
Effective use of persuasion skills will not only help get your coworkers excited about your ideas but also help you motivate them to achieve a common goal.
有效运用说服技能，不仅有助于让同事对你的想法充满热情，还有助于你激励他们去实现共同的目标。
In order to learn the art of persuasion in the workplace, you need to understand how to handle conflicts and reach agreements.
要学会职场中的说服艺术，你需要懂得如何处理冲突、达成一致。
Good communication is the first step in effective persuasion, but logic and reasoning are just as important.
良好的沟通是有效说服的第一步，但逻辑和推理同样重要。
Before you can get somebody on board with your goal, you should help them understand why they should pursue it.
要想让别人支持你的目标，你应该先帮助他们明白为什么应该追求这一目标。
Using visual aids to back up your ideas can help communicate your ideas better and make compelling arguments so your listeners will come to a logical choice and become fully committed to your ideas and plans.
用视觉辅助工具来佐证你的想法，有助于更好地传达这些想法、提出令人信服的论点，从而让听众做出合乎逻辑的选择，并全心全意地拥护你的想法和计划。
Successful persuasion skills are based on your ability to have positive interactions and maintain meaningful relationships with people.
成功的说服技能，建立在你与人积极互动、维系有意义关系的能力之上。
In order to sustain those relationships, you must be able to work in their best interests as well.
为了维系这些关系，你也必须能够从他们的最大利益出发去做事。
Your coworkers are more likely to agree with you when they succeed alongside you.
同事和你一起取得成功时，就更有可能认同你。
The more they achieve and the greater progress they make, the more they trust your judgement and strength.
他们取得的成就越多、进步越大，就越信任你的判断力和实力。
We persuade and get persuaded every day—we’re either convincing or being convinced.
我们每天都在说服别人，也在被别人说服——不是在劝服别人，就是在被别人劝服。
A vast majority of people prefer collaboration and teamwork over traditional organizational structures; no one likes to be told what to do or to be pushed around.
绝大多数人更喜欢协作和团队合作，而不是传统的组织结构；没有人喜欢听别人吩咐自己该做什么，也没有人喜欢被人摆布。
Therefore, organizations and leaders should use powerful persuasion skills to bring about necessary changes.
因此，组织和领导者应该运用强有力的说服技能来促成必要的变革。